myotherdrive.com 2008-12-21

# MyOtherDrive.com - Privacy Statement

**26 January 2006**

The **ByteRocket Privacy Policy** describes how we treat personal information when you use ByteRocket's products and services, including information provided when you use MyOtherDrive. In addition, the following describes our privacy practices that are specific to MyOtherDrive. 

**Personal information**

  * You need a ByteRocket Account to access this site. ByteRocket may ask for some personal information when you create a ByteRocket account, including your alternate passwords, which are used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A ByteRocket Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.
  * ByteRocket stores, processes and maintains your content and other data related to your account in order to provide the service to you.
  * When you use MyOtherDrive, ByteRocket's servers automatically record certain information about your use of MyOtherDrive. Similar to other web services, ByteRocket records information such as account activity (including storage usage, number of log-ins), data displayed or clicked on (including UI elements, ads, links); and other log information (including browser type, IP-address, date and time of access, and referrer URL).

**Uses**

  * ByteRocket maintains and processes your account and its contents to provide the MyOtherDrive service to you and to improve our services. The MyOtherDrive service includes relevant advertising and related links based on the IP address, file content and other information related to your use of MyOtherDrive.
  * ByteRocket may send you information related to MyOtherDrive or other ByteRocket services.

**Information sharing and onward transfer**

  * We provide advertisers only aggregated non-personal information such as the number of times one of their ads was clicked. We do not sell, rent or otherwise share your personal information with any third parties except in the limited circumstances described in the ByteRocket Privacy Policy, such as when we believe we are required to do so by law.

**Your choices**

  * You may change your MyOtherDrive account settings through the MyOtherDrive "settings" section.
  * You may organize or delete your content through your MyOtherDrive account or terminate your account through the ByteRocket Account section of MyOtherDrive settings. Such deletions or terminations will take immediate effect in your account view. Residual copies of deleted content and accounts may take up to 60 days to be deleted from our active servers and may remain in our offline backup systems.
  * You may choose to use additional ByteRocket services, such as ByteRocket Shopping List and ByteRocket Calender.

**More information**

ByteRocket adheres to the US Safe Harbor privacy principles. For more information about the Safe Harbor framework or our registration, see the [Department of Commerce's web site](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).
